This story begins
in Muzaffarpur, a city in Bihar, where there used to be a
huge gap between the number of patients and hospital beds.
Then ICICI Foundation
took a unique step towards cancer treatment and in collaboration with
Homi Bhabha Research Centre of Tata Memorial Centre,
built a new cancer care centre. Patients are coming from all
38 districts and people are also coming here from 10 different states.
So in
2021, we have treated around 12000
patients here and in 2023, it is more than
61000. By donating Rs 1200 crore to Tata Memorial Centre,
ICICI Foundation has
infused new energy in the fight against cancer. With this donation,
three new buildings for cancer care are being constructed in Navi Mumbai, Munapur and Visakhapatnam with state-of-the-art medical
facilities, where
maximum number of people can get cancer treatment at low cost.